[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Viktor! Viktor!
Cute, but we still have a long way to go.
But where are we going?
Forget all those emotions.
It's all nonsense!
Whatever kindness they've shown you,
whatever kindness Mikoy and Chiara
have shown you,
forget all of it.
What matters most of all
is the plan we're all working on.
Forget those emotions.
They don't matter!
Help me serve the food I brought
so our watch party
will be more fun, right?
Come on!
Wait, you know what?
I just remembered.
I have a gift for Chiara.
Wait here, okay?
-Bro.
-I'll leave this to you, okay?
-I'll take care of it.
-Thanks.
Seems like before,
I used to joke about
walking you down the aisle.
Chiara, I am so sure.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Look at my face.
Ouch!
But now,
it's almost here.
Just a little longer,
and it will finally come true.
It's almost like fate was playing a joke
when we first met.
But we also proved, beyond a doubt,
that we really are meant for each other.
I'm listening.
Chiara, I love you so much,
so I accept you.
I didn't want you to find out
about this side of me.
I was so scared you'd find out.
I don't feel worthy of being loved.
Chiara, never say that.
We all deserve to love,
especially you.
But the truth is,
there's only one thing I want.
I just want to be with you.
I can't wait to spend
the rest of my life with you.
You are truly a blessing in my life.
I love you so, so, so much, Chiara.
Mikoy.
What could this be?
So cute!
There's a Chiara too!
Sorry, guys,
if I have to be a killjoy, okay?
But we have a schedule
that you need to follow.
So,
It's time to leave our bride
for the finishing touches.
So come on, let's go, go, go.
Wait. Wait a second.
Chiara, if you need anything,
I'll just be in the next room, okay?
Actually, can I ask you a favor?
Sure. What is it?
My gift for Mikoy.
Okay, sure. I'll get it.
Don't worry, I'll make sure he gets it.
-See you.
-See you!
-Okay go ahead.
-We have to go.
Come on, come on.
No, not like that.
Where's the one doing the retouch?
I want it perfect. You have to look good.
Beautiful, flawless.
Okay, there. That's it.
Okay.
On the count of three,
come closer slowly and smile, okay?
Sir, not much.
Okay.
Okay, one, two, three, look at me.
-Mikoy, Mikoy.
-A little more.
He said don't show your teeth.
Just like that.
-There.
-Okay, okay.
-My goodness.
-There.
How do I do that?
Like that.
Like that, right?
But, son,
that's really part of it, okay?
You have to own it.
You have to feel like you're GGSS.
-There!
-GGSS!
-Okay, okay, okay.
-It's easy. Try it.
Okay, try.
Still not it.
-One more, one more.
-One more.
-How are you supposed to smile, sir?
-Relax.
Just relax.
-Let's just relax.
-Okay.
Mikoy, just relax.
If you don't overthink your smile,
your natural charm
will come out even more.
Right.
Okay, okay, sure.
-Again.
-Okay.
Look into the distance.
Look at me, one, two, three.
-There you go!
-You got it!
You're really good, Agent Alex!
Agent is all we need.
Oh, and Chiara
asked me to give this to you.
Her gift.
That you're the kind of person
I could never get tired of talking to,
teasing, and drinking with.
Ben!
Looks like we're short on soft drinks.
Go get some from the pantry, okay?
Right.
Yes, General.
I went over your profiling report
on the immediate community in Albay.
It seems a little too ordinary.
Nothing stands out.
That's the tricky part.
Sometimes something ordinary can also mean
there's something too good to be true.
Someone stood out to me.
Really, sir?
Who?
That vlogger.
Rahmboy.
That's the one.
Ben!
Where is he?
Be careful.
Especially around Agent Alex.
Nothing changes in the plan.
We're going through with it.
Sofie!
There you go, there you go.
Just a second.
Hey!
-Oh, geez.
-Wait, wait.
I know you’re not talking to anyone.
Sofie.
He passed out!
Let me just confirm something.
The one I sent you,
that's Cocoy's car, right?
Yes, it is.
It's his,
and it's confirmed that Cocoy isn't here.
And Carlota isn't here either.
That's why they weren't responding
in the group chat earlier.
I thought they were with the remote team
this whole time,
but it turns out they're with Team Albay.
-What? They're both here?
-Yes.
Wait, guys, we have an update.
Someone I know said
someone broke Viktor out
last night, there.
Looks like she escaped too.
What? What's happening?
And who would break them out?
Unless the Valtrovis are here.
Angelito?
Angelito.
You're too slow.
I'll do mouth-to-mouth. I'll do it.
Hold that.
Hold this. Hurry up.
Move aside. Go on, do it. Go!
Hey, what do you mean, you?
I'm doing the mouth-to-mouth!
Get out of there!
-All of you, move!
-Come on.
Angelito.
You're taking too long.
Hurry! Come on, hurry!
-You’re too slow!
-So slow.
Wait, wait, wait!
It's my first time!
Just leave them.
They'll come back.
Did I hear that right?
General Norberto said so.
I understand if you're surprised.
It's more than just a surprise, sir.
We're completely shook!
Sir,
it's a good thing
the higher-ups agreed to this,
because they know Viktor and his people
are a high-profile case.
I just thought that since
Chiara killed La Morte Bianca,
and we secured the bomb,
for the two of them.
I agree, sir.
I'm sure Chiara must
be very happy right now.
Sir, didn't that favor you asked for
come with a price, too?
That's right, sir.
The higher-ups might come after you.
His sudden transfer of Viktor and Brusko
to a highly secured prison,
on top of the string of violence
that happened inside.
With what he did,
it's very obvious
that he has it out for Viktor.
Exactly. You're absolutely right, sir.
But knowing Senator Quintin's connections,
sooner or later,
you might get a memo about this.
For now, just think of me as a boss
who isn't a killjoy.
And since I rarely ask
the higher-ups for a favor,
-One for the books, that's for sure!
-Yes.
More pizza!
Hey, Sofie!
Don't avoid me now.
Me?
Weren't you the one
avoiding me all this time?
How does it feel
to be the one being avoided?
Awkward, isn't it?
How does it feel to be
on the receiving end?
Just because we got drunk the other day
doesn't mean any of that wasn't real.
Because
the truth is,
I like you.
That's your answer? Okay?
You're so nonchalant.
Or we could go with "bebu."
Then,
love.
The bride isn't done yet!
She'll come out according to our schedule.
Keep going.
You're so persistent!
She's really not done yet!
I'm sorry, no offense, but it's important.
There's a surprise for the bride.
Senator, there's bad news.
What is it?
Viktor escaped, along with Donabel.
How did that happen?
When?
Just last night.
It was sudden.
Looks like someone
up top gave the go-ahead.
Someone had the nerve to bypass me?
And who are these annoying people?
She's so beautiful, Viktor. Look at her.
That's nothing. Look, I have another one.
My child.
Sorry, okay? This is all we could manage.
Here's another one. Look.
Sorry, but I was the one
who picked all of these.
Chiara.
It all happened so suddenly, right?
We didn't expect we'd be able to make it.
-Exactly.
-Your father and I are so happy.
What an irony.
Back when we were living the good life,
we could easily
get you anything you wanted.
Everything was within reach.
Yes, that's true.
Remember, honey?
Oh, my gosh.
We used to shop like crazy!
Right? You know that.
You always knew how much our bill was.
We really shopped like crazy.
The shopping couldn't keep up with us.
I remember this one time,
we bought so much stuff, and then
we just gave it all to the saleslady.
And they were so shocked.
Because they thought it was
a prank.
Like some social experiment.
We just didn't know
what to do with our money
back then.
But seriously.
I really thought
you wouldn't be able
to make it to my wedding.
You know,
I'm really getting stressed out
because of that GAGO.
I'm so stressed, I need to schedule
a session with my doctor.
Your doctor already went abroad.
When will they be back? No!
Call them and tell them
this is an urgent matter.
Tell them to come home.
Apparently, even your doctor
is now being investigated by GAGO agents.
Son of a…
tofu!
And apparently, you're
next on their list to investigate.
They won't find anything
in their investigation.
I have solid connections
in different government departments!
Let them try me.
I'm just not going to let
myself be the only one stressed out.
I don't want them to be
the only ones having fun.
La Morte Bianca's Mama Yaya?
Your nanny when you trained in Sicily?
Love wears many faces.
There are many ways to care
and many ways to sacrifice.
But we are always have to choose.
There's always a decision to make.
And until the very end,
I will choose to love
in the only way I know how.
For the person I love most.
MJ? What's the update?
Why is it taking so long
for the door to open?
MJ. MJ!